<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gmenu</string>
    <string name="toast_issue_1">Sorry. You should have at least two language skill to be Guider.</string>
    <string name="toast_issue_2">Please input at least 30 letters for bio</string>
    <string name="label_logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="title_slide_1">Private Data We Receive And Collect</string>
    <string name="description_slide_1">
قم بالذهاب إلى المطعم<br/>
الذي تريده والجلوس على أي<br/>
طاولة تحتوي على رمز QR</string>
    <string name="title_slide_2">How We Use Evolo Landing Page Data</string>
    <string name="description_slide_2">
قم بفتح التطبيق الخاص بنا<br/>
وتوجيه هاتفك نحو صورة<br/>
رمز QR الموجودة أمامك</string>
    <string name="title_slide_3">Customer Content We Process For Customers</string>
    <string name="description_slide_3">
ستظهر لك صفحة جديدة في<br/>
التطبيق تحتوي على جميع أطباق<br/>
ووجبات المطعم المتواجد به</string>
    <string name="title_slide_4">Consent Of Using Evolo Landing Page</string>
    <string name="description_slide_4">By using any of the Services, or submitting or collecting any Personal Information via the Services, you consent to the collection, transfer, storage disclosure, and use of your Personal Information in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy. If you do not consent to the use of your Personal Information in these ways, please stop using the Services.</string>
    <string name="title_slide_5">Inquire What Data We Have</string>
    <string name="description_slide_5">Evolo Landing Page uses tracking technology on the landing page, in the Applications, and in the Platforms, including mobile application identifiers and a unique Evolo user ID to help us recognize you across different Services, to monitor usage and web traffic routing for the Services, and to customize and improve the Services.  \n\n\n By visiting Evolo or using the Services you agree to the use of cookies in your browser and HTML-based emails. Cookies are small text files placed on your device when you visit a Cookies are small text files placed on your device when you visit a Cookies are small text files placed on your device when web site in order to track.</string>

</resources>